oh it on line
oh uh
i haven't kept moved here i'm starting back still going to one another here they're the weather too
no limit to judge like well on the way he didn't divorce
hello
a lot of time
mister robot down here in portland
old
stuck more technical revenge energy going downhill people don't make
wind your way one town one around liberal they would hold onto and all that goes on the year they did them
oh my
yeah no they loved over new and see shirt a thing going on it's really really good
that one is thirty years old they are going out rather than
celebrity for god when they know
you know what to do go in the quarter lord yard to buy your neighbor to no good on warm than money
oh there are laws love
oh yeah i know we're so crazy real real about it again
water that were running
okay oh you're about to what was your
there's another book i don't even know
oh um