gotten yeah you're living in college yeah she's a wheelchair
are you
sable yeah homeless disabled living in a tent north carolina it's gotta be horrible it's not good
what do you survive grace of god no way
well i've got food stamps and people bring cigarettes cigarettes mountain dew how long you been here sixteen years sixteen years you been right
wow it totally or never said totally homeless for or sixty you've adapted well not really okay tell me about
it's hard you know and it's every day and there's no inside
no
spend hundreds of thousands millions of dollars to shut down the toilet but there's not a time to help us shelters stress in a shelter i cannot do that's why i'm here
um
for lack of a better word is it's so unnecessary
people are always talking about the money you know put a price on misery
we have no medicine we have no money now they want to take away the panhandlers licenses is how most all of these people make a little money that they have me i don't even have that because i'm sick to go up there every day it's like a mile each way in and out to the nearest bus stop i have to travel two miles just to begin to go anywhere plus i have no money for bus and i don't have the energy anymore it's just wipe me out every day takes a piece on what your future future future throwing myself in front of these you know when i can't take it anymore sixteen years is a long time to talk about uh future under these circumstances is ridiculous i mean it's just
yeah it's would be like world peace
like a cold beer cigarette store i don't have to worry
i'm just kidding thank you very much for talking