yeah and and uh
yeah nah
yeah you've got your hall we day i've gone to dollars dollar
i'm dave yard a half years
hi got
see i always found him memorial day
yeah um
no man not bother about um i didn't go man um
oh yeah i mean where we can blame adam
okay and um
and now i'm not a family maybe with the wind on them and go
oh last bottom dollar um um
big big uh
man yeah right
oh okay
oh man
yeah they have
not bottles house of books
um and goals man to my father's come and go to my father's house
it's a big big house where there's nothing left so real
oh bang bang bang bang ya where we can't play ball um bang bang
oh yeah oh oh man
this my father
mm mhm