hi i'm jackie
down down down down down down down down down there and i asked you know take a while while we're leaving to go to stores and let me know but a little restaurants
and then they but do
none that i know a day to day
they all mind you know and then you know and then i got a good job was great to know what i want to do that in order to be a bit way white people they don't call it a job
as long as they do and then the day day in the winter time during the last time we were married and they you know the other one million dollars
and then
know
yes
and then they do that and then the direction and i do too points and bad humor and and and and the pound and number one number two number and then and
jeeze