um
mm
we can
you don't know it's like you say you can to and club and the
oh
which uh paint number
mm see shows were you
uh-huh to same time
you know that's just uh
right
on the news on t._v. or man of this
and all that stuff yeah she's going to get ready to go and say hey jennifer
marriages or and my parents are married too
right no money type thing
yeah
mhm yeah yeah uh-huh well i believe on that
mhm mhm mhm right well
no yeah like more the other day real real bad business and just
this is the way this is
he's not he's real picky tearing into real estate investor touch last dog mall and vote they gotta go where they try to i usually just real ticketed if you'd be able to do three ninety nine k._t._l._a. lifestyle chad
report