that is just to be near not only does in his mother his girlfriend
i'm sure
most competent mostly on the mood is amazing and says the humidity is nutrition and
mhm
hey uh she says uh to that series or lose and you expect to see and and his girlfriend
eastern worried twenty three or national you you
yeah he's he's he seems to be able to
'cause you do more activities to do the same as clear as middle savings or whatever mushrooms
yeah do you have
twenty four years
actually my sister lives kept coming back
now i live in those
there's too the longer than that he or she carnegie mellon roses don't belong
and they're both in rogers dale
they need you need 'em you know
yeah then
yeah
mhm yeah yeah yeah mhm