hi my name's sandy bottom west here at the edge performance facility here and killer texas
go through squat technique today to help you
i do a little bit better form my things to help the form of be correct on squad squad to get a bad rap because there are bad on your back and they're bad on your knees and they are if you're doing wrong if you're doing
it's the best exercises that you can do for a lower body squats again um universal left again
people do them wrong a lot so weird help you see the right way to do squats starting off
you to make sure the bar for most people you wanna make sure the bars right about chess level if it gets higher than that it's hard to get underneath if it's too low
i get an extra rep and there to get her name and get it so you want to make the the bar without chester shoulder hyped here
for someone to go over cigarettes this is approximately how most standard bars
two little rings little grip brings there they are approximately thirty two inches apart for most people that i had to do is take their index finger and place it on the ranks
yeah same here
she would take your index finger place it on the ranks so now i got a nice even grip at the start of the moving a lot of people going to need the bar they revert wrong suppose off kilter heavier
fried dust again promoters lower back and she's so
even even grip that step one step
now i'm going to step on to the bar i get a park placement on my back on the top quarter my shoulders i'm gonna show you the wrong way first and then the writer
um the wrong way a lot people will get up here and they'll get a high bar squat like say some piling net okay there's not a lot of
you're talking about a four inch area it's a little pinnacle on my knee on my on my next year and so and peters alot again a lot of problems on lower back a pilot but so we're gonna teach you out
it's too low heart places where it goes below other tracks and between the shoulder blades right here in this area so american
yes and all the trap get there a high morally wrong way it's a little more now the problem with the low bar squat
that there was like it's written your shoulder blades outlook socket
okay you gotta teach maybe uh individuals are like had to get their elbows up like this was watching it
which is here it's on a table up there it's covered
fifteen to twenty inches now as opposed to the poor insurance a pilot
you take your new i can't use to us
ability to develop this
but it'll be now that station number two they're got the bar placements refrained gotta get your feet right you got
stab each year you better darryl stance you got to why can't worry more conventional stand on the stand
to do if you like have our toes
watch out for the ducks okay you know what your feet spread out like to make sure they're
for most people when it first started but we try to do just go somewhere and just outside shoulders outside shoulder with those
straight out that i really don't see the first thing you do the first moon butter the first man
honest schwab is when you're not sure i mean
well here that's why you watch it a bad rap
it's my niece burning up so much tore gone up too much pressure it's bad on your knees and and also go into your back
going to push our hips back person like we wish they would kick the door shut that were in some kicking the door shut kick the door
back there now my hips for back now i'm starting to stand in the squad pushy
this and he's about like the flats that'd you get a shot at my feet down her go to
the is on the outside of my foot and on my field is not up in in on my toes case
my hamster back i'm exaggerating my team here it's either going to say slack and then i come back up
so it has something to do a few restaurants you can see that push your habits
don't go outside of a slow motion backup just now to about parallel and back uh
my knees will never drift over my toes wants money these over my toes
that is bad for pushes back like
out oh my gosh sitting on a horse i'm going to be like this my name is actually in a flair outlets so i'm here like this is my new nasal starts
but my abdominal oh down in between my name is
just like that's a kind of exaggerate when my age what we're putting out here like that
and that's a form on the squats as far as getting parallels push your hips back helping you give her though i've been standing back up when you iraq to bar mature somebody hell she spots we'll talk
about a second what's that uh get back into iraq at least of our earliest
big key where people get hurt 'cause when they pick the bar up and when they said the bar down when you pick the bar up make sure you use both feet to pick it up like a school
don't get in there like you're doing the lunch to try to pick it up it's all on your butt
quarter back to the same way we could back in her released it down with both legs don't lean into it um like you're going to watch the spot
we spot somebody with a guy find a guy or a male or squatting you're going to spotted underneath the chest you kind of coming up behind him help him up this way when the lady and squatting or one of the girl athletes you're going to spot what we call the w. w. b.
are you going to put your hand right there and kind of spot the bar if you have
on the side and never ever have one person pick up and the other one's chicken it's just bought the given you should have the heads far behind them say take it then they get all free
there's nothing worse to get in four or five hundred pounds on your back you get down there like there's so many grabbed one side bad on your back better
so it could be like on the spot or israel spiders be careful um
that's the basis on the spot and that's the basic on the school
and again this is danny at the ashworth performance you any questions you
at her number down at the bottom two screen or a website is w. w. w.
that edge dash s. p. dot com