what's the elmo helping dad
dinosaurs shirt with matching cool
he speaks
a stuffed animal not really interested sucks ooh no candy that easter bunny stinks and a book
hi five years and he likes his book mace
me too
get him to they may say oh that's a big book
hey hey
it's amazing
yeah he is sitting down and look at it with them
or
you're pretty good reader mace mason
hi huh
can you know what you're getting in play
try to get him to watch
oh okay oh how close
what's that fat cat doing out there he's given capable
your legs a little wobbly this morning
hi can you wait nice base can you
is it is
what do you think you're doing what do you think you're doing
a monkey