the morning to glue and um
inward recently saw shape it to get that sort of spirals look and then um before i go up here i i always love the snow and the little areas because i couldn't wider them in perfectly that would take more time i don't want to do that i should say not a one person job you've got to be a little out of your mind to do this by yourself but you know so there's that and
recycle are over there i might spray down these water will find out you have two smaller bricks him too
okay about three quarters up doing this last year and i'm using them in half it's working
we have the recycled have door i can move 'em all in here
at a time really cut in half so far they've been working out good uh starting stack them up around just keep going up you know we get in there now this is about five times larger than i planned to just kinda going up but it has a child we should be done
um i've gotten up to the top top been real tricky it's just wherever stays crumbling for some reason they weren't must be getting twenty but we're just not ready for the headstone
okay i'm in an igloo sealed you can see the roof stands about almost seven feet tall inside probably eight feet outside
alright next one next week camping in this thing probably tonight
hello
i finish my i grew up a little bit right around here it's about
it's about uh i'd say about sixty five inches tall about eight feet on top water on top the bucket of water all over that freeze up
we're looking good from the outside boston up a little bit
sure interested morrow
here's yes
alright nice officially done very excited about twice the size but that's okay and are campus that should be free