oh you live at fort lauderdale
hi my my own ways and go but i never i never met i tried that
i tell good for you or you know there is a good way i felt like it's about a limited so simply because
in most write about at one time
i know i might
similar but he always a little bit on it was much more friends are going to fight if i didn't clay i think that's probably
not even close to him but they showed you know
and that kind of and i'll tell you what was that was all plug it into the news rundown
thank you so what i said i was safer than anything related i can't believe that thing
i mean you don't really find i what you know supply anyway
i can't do without the method of money how age they find work out well how are you know
i guess that's how i mean up tightened titans larry of work i know where to play the more you know i don't know i'm not working right now
you know try to do that need to find say that we love it but
living anyway