yeah down here in san yeah i don't know i mean i don't know so right off got to be a problem and i went by the time was all
eighteen
i'm going to get on the other side and then my
you're still you up a little bit
yeah 'cause they're more like a level too
and leave it up there and then maybe she'll want to feel that you want to do your it's gonna work
stick it in schools because you more deeply here
the cleaner primer first and that's that sets up the action for the glue
roughly about thirty seconds totally things from
it's always good to have a twisting motion when you first joined them together and just that into the socket that's good
i did before four inches because they raised the size of the one one happened diameter to there and one inch diameter bowls but now there's two inch one and a half inch i've got all the other ones
that's from there to the ground to measure that um that that definitely that they should all this
you know
yeah they do is let your bottom line you know what
that's really good yeah i don't think you got you know prepare mm
yeah maybe that extra half
we can live without them and and was just
mhm
because my parents then i got we got eight and we should have gotten pregnant yeah that where we need to going on at all
and um
well why do we just had that might be easier
how are you at
okay and then with the level on
yeah
that are getting putting a school here and here
mhm
oh my god how much