hey welcome to new hampshire my name's i'm a student here jack mountains taking ten week skills semester program let me show you what we've been up to the first week
a nine year old daughter
the the the
then then then then they get a little bit
so you just finished shelter it's really really comfortable got room for storage for my feelings underneath
i'm already gonna be projects are hearing the framework home sweet home bigger the fire more violently you can
no
maybe a little snack corner corner and i want them all in the same plane meaning one spiral around hit the ball you guys are going to have an internal you'll know exactly what she was exactly how to get there there's no way
well not work to go ahead
so i'm working on my hand and try to get it perfectly on the trial and error
okay let's go back to see that the camera
the more stronger the world
i look forward on rolls around you can really aches so uh let me show you the shelter i spent last
i built this on friday afternoon yesterday using the same techniques that we learned on monday to build build our big shelters were spending a whole week and a year that's more the uh netting and the plastic sheeting uh here's my bed
uh we're going to be learning about all natural shelters later on but now this is a time saver makes a really good shelter
kept me nice and warm last night even though it was raining kinda chilling can't wait to see what i learned actually that's it for the first week here at the skill semester program a jack mountains come back again next week and see what we have in store
now they are the little guy
then they go down there
and then the