uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh
huh
but eh but lives gags me back in time and they're saying no longer
make up your mind but i do know redoing man no recreating redo that
why do you wanna sit down with new york
oh is it
hey
full and ya oh man so who is what
oh and gas
you take off him do to notice
good how are you in that room preview on no accident and she goes to move move
um is it is to you too
yeah do they ever really
and uh uh and then
oh man yeah to quit
what school who watch and you know so who is
yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah coffee also you know
okay we they were there but he all know that saying and tune into a room
um era it is yeah well you see
yeah me too
gary yeah the yeah they