love is they're burning
and it to make up higher rewrite
oh wow wow
i fell into a ring like fire and
i went down down down and let's landers slander i i used by
hi er rank up to pie
ah to burn ring up by how much um now i'm not blaming loyal
as burns learn and
no desire to surveying up an age awful love is sleep
one of the largest black scholars
i feel for your like a child and
oh what the firemen wild
well then i went down down down lame is more of fire
and it's our priorities barn and then
hey by by any means
decide to do uh burning rang liar i went with um um lame
and it just turns burns burning
why are raymond by
or
by being ring him or the ring up by the ring