well
but
mm
oh
gave me ah
and then there's one thing you could you help me show you plant here uh
mm mm so
uh
sure oh man
you know but um
um show me a
me
and
you know a day five huge game basically
um and then and then they
give me a a
they give me show you are right you mean ah
well i'm on the internet
what do you think right
that's true do you do any of this year
not really totally totally if you got the magic surprise party you know physical cost
so how can how can there anyway
we gave them when you're twenty okay we can pull that off and think about it i believe be twenty years
the country yeah last year and a lot of the walker now and what was your favorite part of the record
you know they don't want to
one
everything was okay i was pretty good one
that was my birthday okay well yeah
oh yeah oh yeah we had a day
yeah yeah
oh my god oh my god
better
i'm not saying that it was and i'm a and then the time there was a man