what's your again i guess and i don't get too young for a few years i don't see any of these other multivitamin the it's not going to be able to tell me uh uh i mean you know but it's okay if you well actually i mean you well uh i was you know that he's on on the homes
uh uh
what a lot in the uh then you don't
i just saw so yeah i guess you can add that on the seven day
yeah that's funny
you know i don't usually
well i think i am today and do you when you let the joe millionaire
huh
i get to the phone book or the was it about the you can say that you are are watching it get to a that you don't have that well what do you think so too so yeah
that's nothing
yeah
oh for sure
just on the day then you get to know if i don't get many continuing thank you well yeah that's i just from the uh but uh they get to get into