hello okay hanging then we then i make the u._n.
okay good good enough that that i think there oh what's your name
really so much fun time now okay um
that is not your head to the oh sure
can you keep you had the same stories from my heart that that'd be good to have
we got not just about the ethnic
well no no it's not blowing up we know yes i have a dog and we can say is dying bathing suit
none of god they oh not that
because you're the moslem well the heck well
i'm fine and a half or thought it was no me whether or not i got fired offensive always where
yeah like i don't enjoy your state run anybody made up and then you ah not not hired came well god