mhm
yes
man
standing on the border checking the border
died down down by the door county sign up but you know
you know new york new york and new york
down here down in miami anywhere anymore you know what i'm looking for that down and you have anything and they have a every time you are fine
being to be out in the in long beach
you know when you eat them up and do the mountain
new jersey and you know i know new york or new
they're down here to do that anymore you know what i'm looking for now they they found every time
you know new new
touch down around on see you around
you are
i'm looking for chinatown thing down here we have by the time down care about any new walking down everything
no