right but then you're sentiment month you have to put this
nope i you have to help mommy's front need your help get the ball take a ball and put it on the pan good good job on line too
they're already fantastic
for me anymore
fine yeah it is it the sugar and the taste
and get paid
i mean is it good uh better get a little bit more yeah great job pays better rules cookies
are you in charge of the sentiment sentiment
some what do you guys baking cookies
put any cookies there's a cookie monster like cookies
which pretty much to say sheesh sins tastes
hey steve tastes we got to get
fair lady cheaper going to think you ate too many cookies in that rod it out
so what does a cookie monster say let's cookie say
no it was clicking lots to say what's he say hey
i it caucasian race mm
and uh you gotta wait wait a minute wait let's these up for that 'cause my experience dream lax and then you can have a taste after we put 'em on the pan
well look at the i'm and those must be hot spell bell hi hot on his hands
one
okay sure to excellent and three
her she said now you can have advocate
unlike
hey good mental makes them more okay and then the little things beep beep beep
and then we can start good work