and uh
oh
accounting welcome to my brother's car we really really would like to to blow the car and a couple of reasons why burning fire
there's also a huge difference
oh
oh wow
beer x-rays
they're christening ship racing strike
well the starches all bad it's perfect for yoga
they're
my brother chevy astro van this car is one big piece of garbage um it does drive by a couple of things have happened yesterday i think to be honest with you he could really use a new car frustrated please just blow this vehicle so he can get a new car because the poor guy he's car based upon all the stuff that he's gone through
blow up i stuck up here