oh oh
thank you
they make you guys are aware but we have been on raising guys this one true but if somebody's birthday or only give your friends
have you at all
you know unless we burn it or not
probably better so i think
and uh and time
oh first or second a book in the paper the other oh smoking or not but this is a ticket to the james uh does it on
oh i didn't want to get over a year
and don't don't think about there and and uh
i'm gonna make it also the right to censor things obviously a little belly
hum
think of flattering for her she really finches or her weight i think it really gets our grabbing her hair well to the natural kind of girl is one of his name is brian exactly the thing about in the summer than i do i really like the great the museum oh good hold my hand