hi everybody is gonna help me big his no no we're not going to be or you just touched eggs bake his um his second birthday so started maxwell put in here yeah maybe
no
there we go can you can put this in here oh good job good job with this
mm mm
good job
mhm
the ingredients may not be perfect measurement but that's okay here we go
yeah that goes on here we go alright all this way
alright no hold on one second i really can't um
yeah you push the button to push this button
mhm
oh okay
oh all right here's a life partner reading he put this in the ball
mhm
good
alright let me for the simple good job thank you okay what about this for the bowl sour cream yeah
okay alright so our kareem
the sugar to put the sugar
ah alright and the butter yeah
perfect
good job right now it's not real good
everybody everybody mr oh good job good job yes so good good job thank you
alright let's do a little bit more okay really fast or
no no
good job slow uh
yes
oh i just one more time
alright
really part
let's look at the top for this in here and there
good
good job of course we don't daddy does not have any history of course that dirty soon oh
good job easter job yeah we're got a good you're doing so good
alright so you will come back when we're eating our cake by everyone