the you have a to send some uh you know i've also got a but i don't care you
it's gonna some students but
let's see
you know uh play a a human being but yeah um well i don't i think students but you
luckily i uh you see a a you know what it is for uh for the community that's
mhm
you can
you don't see them pretty bad enough times italian this usually the maximum that you i'm from to keep up to date
well for
okay a lot of on on and uh yeah she was then or i'm i'm from like she was they say well okay a marshal who just don't know what to do something like that
going to keep your stomach so she's
okay yeah the dr on the
you don't
but or
what do they uh uh she was suing showing that you don't get a sense don't she did with sickle cell yeah well you don't see a much
yes