okay i got some real real good
okay now we're going to try to take
okay on yours that a little about that what they mm
tastes like they slice pad that very well
mm
okay you don't need that why have a if you want to put it over where
mm really want to give it to right that's very possible
you don't need it cooking i walk on nightmare
how about if i use in charlotte would you care for peace darling may they get really no pineapple okay i will cut she'll piece without pineapple
was if you like it you want my son when he uses them
he did a good job my darling gabby thank you manny charlotte which he likes them
cream on yours that way this yeah
yes or no no no thank you
but her yahoo sweet so
never learned he said thank you yeah i'm fine