mm mm
and we're gonna a or talk to them and make sure that before you go your your bronco you don't get
so they have
one of one a couple of nothing but one and a half of the floor one people making make sure that you have your cooking and so many such as you are measuring 21 so we have it from one tablespoon all the way down to watch you're you're you're mixing bowl and all your this is going to be our dating fan
okay and they start taking so we do our dining room for so we have here one and half cups of floors me for my new mark that even and on the table because that is right
oh yeah
now we have our children so we'll see this is already do we put everything on there
great
next for are making so we put down there
everything
right
and now i'm in oregon
then they did one call
let me put it down there
but then all that you can
now we have your
and then
and make sure that he's not actors to make sure you have either or that you don't have any and
maybe either with with me to make them a lot or you can add any ingredients you make it
really really to
an ad or to to make sure that it down there so you so everything comes out so that this looks young
mhm
so we've got it on there and make sure you can use a mixture of another one or you can do and when he depends on every night
no
years and years and um what are they
and make sure your three year old baby three hundred fifty degrees so now the
make sure your
they try everything in there for anything
we have a gown and he put the insight on that
you get your gonna wait for things now you can either you can expect to check the consistency if you're in oregon so we're gonna check ours now
doing good and make sure you have something called
so have you had
now me for it before you started at the very
so that everybody and get hurt
now they have all um miniature
ten minutes and get your name again mhm
but the or your family
they're getting
so we over something something so we have here but the ice cream they were going to make some
get the same thing but on top and say if you want to put some chocolate but it's pretty good like that
that's
perfect for kids and adults anyway the chocolate lovers
like i don't know
that's