yeah
hi how do you like uh i think so we have indian bench and all kinds of stuff you know 'cause look nice
mhm
so how long they say gosh i haven't a clue about fan not bad for the better but we got there first cope use nearly a gallon they said that we do two coats easy peasy lives so uh we'll see what this looks like when i'm driving to get a second code on it
see so much people made our standards not very high
and it is the day after our initial paint session
yeah down here and
we're trying to terminate if we actually need a second there hopefully we don't
and
for me that we probably do need to
a lot of white spots and put another coat on which i think it's more accurate
very good sounds good health or and we did actually picked out a couple of other colors uh yesterday we picked so the green don't delete and we pick out some paint today actually for the bathroom so here's the uh the bathroom here christmas bringing you know it's kind of just a color we originally doing that for the master christian in there so she does like however and the other so thinking about doing that and that plus eat some painting on 'cause we got fireworks go through life