well your email i'm all for good
making cooking harris hey you're making them
um saint yes or no
you'd licking fingers
now what do you do is just so she where are you doing right now
oh okay what kind of look kinda cookies are they
we ended up being on the back of your insurance
absolutely
christmas cooking inclined christmas sprinkle a cookie oh okay
yeah i've even cook them yet there's already on me you do put lots of good sprinkles on your cookies
yeah it's a good
oh okay okay me reagan wanted to do it hurts now you really
how the cookies
who are you making the cookies for um plenty ends meet
oh it is eddie kidding okay i met they're going to be really good cookies
yeah that's a good job
yeah on um they know the guy putting now what do we do with him
oh and that's on that will sit on that p._i._n. what do we worst we put the pin
i hate cooking day and and the cooking thing okay we'll do that and then when they're done we're gonna take
what is what does it circle around
good okay so he cook a cookie okay well get picture on there all day
hi