uh
you know how to break up the girls the college loans well certainly in the military so
no
i was
it's in the and no you don't want to do is i have garlic itself after you were allowed to last
and sat around three other guys and and they make so much divorce
are you recording all this stuff you know i said at four hundred man
ready instead of looking for something new you know how to cook so i don't know how to
is actually no it doesn't seem like i can't put them in the town they have one i always turn it down to seven temperatures research and they friends
right well this is supposed to go into things and they just put in the others usually when i cook there's nobody around to distract had to go to the the the main characters meat fish that's so we didn't need the the um in the evening you know not
are you on board for you know going through this
close personal
mine's making food lots of leftovers
and definitely
you can pull that they're have have
the only woman like they make some but we will send you some money uh um i have to deal with doesn't eat by or
for your birthday want to cook
well then also your water
the very day per day do you have a birthday party i knew
well i was going on
um no no no no
that is of one those too
yeah the first step myself today initially going through the lawsuits
oh no it's really inside that it's all good