what's your go ahead and get to what it is and that's you know what she she or do something uh you don't get it
um the the or put out uh i don't i mean ah i'm sure the you don't i'm i'm in one country
uh yeah i think it's don't go keep up with
yeah
yeah i've been thinking i don't know it wasn't so
i'm didn't sell
i think that's fine but down the line on what's your news from the
i'm pretty i'm pretty challenging
yes
it was in
i mean
know some of them is that normal showing
that's when it gets it should be
well i think i'm you get through that but the a of 'em are gonna a a single mom i get to one guy uh uh you can only don't they don't get told tonight you know you get to that spaghetti uh you get to a she was people didn't even young when i saw an academy or you don't go to some nice people you got to go to a a to me uh i don't really see or go to a yeah
up in st i think balance
huh
and get to yeah yeah she makes the most you can get to a uh