no no no no no no no nine
hi kitchen today feed than i am going to be making some oh yeah all these ingredients you go yeah creme is well hundred flower yet two eggs yeah for presentation like a hundred and fifty baking cases presentation hundred and twenty five grams of playing chocolate and the the first thing we are going to do is actually created together in the in a boat and starting around what we're going to do something like that so let's get going fishing right now is the cases in tracing you got kids as being gotta plugged that in that on sugar and as well we give until it to in the meantime well she's not and beat them together so she's finished and she's now moved on stomachs good what we're going to do is i never going to pull the egg makes just gradually like this in in well and stuff and the rest of us getting that the flower already in any minute now give it a couple of minutes i think yeah like basically this is a celebration flowers looking good support a little bad time okay and then they're not until it's all going as well so what she's doing a fall with little teeny bit they just got to in a round together to make a little so pasty thing for the most so now all of this stuff for him such as to the ball
yeah
okay so um cases uh used to play with the chocolate while you do this or i don't think i'm i'm in the cream get on to start to break up chocolate while you're waiting for okay so that take off the heat and our garbage not just on the heat and the i started to blend together and the chocolate or again boy that's gonna be off the heat up take off and again just the same as we did just an easy peasy that is probably way i'm so i take away the heat again until they also joining with the chocolate mixture okay and uh yeah we were getting blended in now you know it's just leave to down and see my oven on these shows about fifteen minutes probably turn around and the kids getting on how you doing buddy someone going to be clean i think the same opportunity to get get cleaned up while they're in the oven phoebe yeah he needs how they're gonna stay go anyways push the buttons on the safe the powder when are we talking afterwards but we got fifteen minutes i like t._v. say changed but after that um anyway what about these cakes ready so let's see that
yeah wow they smell and you have up these
good um so anyway let's get them i guess yeah yeah so let's take down on the states as well say coming together down right down the well so they start to spend on a she was just creme
must of the uh
the cream um on the cakes and each one of the way to start speaking this mixture onto the case so i just finished reading the chocolate makes you or the scrappy cream and for example and this one little thing but i do that on each of your cupcakes right cool getting crazy with the first too but um the rest of the sprinkler lightly okay i just finished putting some chocolate buttons on on the party so we so uh yeah dinnertime take little bit okay me game i think
to face is that nice
extreme