to make a chocolate cake you will need a hundred grams of chocolate
two hundred grams of flour
hundred grams of it
a hundred grams of sugar
now summary of the ingredients
you will need the following you so
you will need
a big
and now the small summary essential
you have to print given at fifty degrees
you off to the movies
then put the flowers alone for the cake to stick
break the chocolate in then put it into some
pcs into some milk
the most and better and the
mix the butter and the
then
then and the eggs into them extra stuff
in a mixture
then i
mix
we don't want any lumps
a bucket of east
then put the mixture of the
put into the the maximum temperature for five minutes
after five minutes to the normal temperature well for forty minutes
no cooked with a knife it's screen is well cooked mm
and then and then and then you know and i don't know