easter sunday which is something katie
yes i did i do um
right okay well let's see if we can monitor remember each having a two and a guy that's got
what is your fun
to get some nice to know my um let's see well
what did you get
yeah
did you get how many
wow
you going to keep you really gotta keep the to get some yeah
wow james
really
right
i just became a grandma separate or
really
mhm
oh
to get um
is it is
you know
the company
i
can you
yeah i wanted to stay in because oh my goodness me we've got tons in here
that's what
really well done
mhm
see more
really good at finding exactly see anymore
mhm
i think that's just about it then well i think you will be thoroughly spoiled add them up in
right
you know a good one are you sure can see what money for