people who are when he when he he do
for some time to change some place to go hand in the fruit juice and and and it gets
the difficulty of plus uh
i'm just saying you have any other shows
plus the i've been listening to what she doesn't she give you a teacher
you you
you're in and you were up in
to have it done today that gets me
you can actually use it
oh you the
no i know
and you said
uh you could just fine a lotta people
yeah well
how about drug testing
it's like you when you come yeah how'd you do on the outside more it's been on it
which is up
i'm just i mean
was young so full of myself you know what are they
no
so i was i felt a lot of funky
oh i don't know sometimes i question
well he he was on the mood okay well see uh