to the cooking and they really simple um well uh the other one's already orange county um
chocolate cake and eat anything in
yeah do you
they tend to educate type 1 diabetes
james what's your opinion on giant okay thanks because it got a sideline
well the other night and then he hasn't come back yeah
a different country so
something or
that's five
so what time has passed yeah i'm
the final pops up i take the last night but you know chocolate milk trucks very easily say some um
see how that works
so so it's cooled down on the carpet 'cause one stuff i put chocolate put it back in the french to kind of off the next round chocolate
the second time
so
somebody now is the and then like truth how such a you know people that i'm into truth again uh that son went into the
all chocolate so choice as to take to tell jokes i just couldn't it probably still pretty good
i'm i'm on the cake last and then a future much less
oh no you can't talk about the first amazing that they try and