mm mhm mhm mm mhm mhm
oh did you travel is also but if you we're supposed to visit him myself but isn't there it's just a national mcdonald's employee how she but um i
saint paul since since you can think of them are just so good since you've been seeing that i must footing
look it's a good time for marketing
it was sad but they'll stop at a it's so good but bulls yeah
but mentioned you louis not this this is going to miss
i i've lived pertinent the seniors students isn't good emily's monday i temperature to them
but at work to it since secrets asian that much to plug in dublin
let's see i see what the movie's not this thinking that must
to steal from sports time for fuzzy it'll saying no bash wherever so long since millage to not
which the me east would been you just mashed at different families should successes
mm mm mm
mm
but sometimes i do normally see jailer give up with a gun
inflation costs books them establish applied
for the buck fifty families that
mm mhm
to of well might hitting
mm mm this concept out style
you too slow for me
but if it didn't last but as soon as you
let's this quite as english skills
mhm
you're just sort of soup pen at least you this is jim
mm mm
mhm
she'll just so good calm if any yes well it's only cousin
this is the maximum so polite um you should find
mm mm
well that's a good yeah you think if people should you didn't take it out good on
mhm
besides computers to florida well if he did some finely wonderful thing
people seem much this one must have done
this is the fifth did see queens of so say somebody thought
mm mm
mhm
mm mhm
yeah well let's talk with them
course this is my point that that dog
lucky for thought there no pets talked
mm
mm mm mm
to discipline that oh my goodness so but if they're still scene
mm mm
keep it some thoughts in will didn't believe
mhm
mm
bush see some but up to the next cause not doesn't bring money
mhm
let me say this much but
still just on students so folks today
mhm
it's good it's school spent washing their sight to see it finished