happy birds or whatever okay ready one two three packs a day to happy birthday to happy birthday any birthday to you
mhm
nice even catch it against them
okay i'm stopping
i i that was they didn't work
to have it i just every birthday every birthday
i think your first birthday you know
what your number was i thin let me have been flicking around by by somewhere i always told me okay
i don't know how
no
that's what i mean i didn't um
oh you know sweet little dog back out
mm
oh see
mm mm
oh man i should try
for me listening to the place and neither long walk said he's to need a long walk wow narrow margin which are backing it it's need to eat my dinner we just have to put in in my i either
been a baby boy