well let me at all
yeah when i don't watch
okay
man
oh i play whatever that is how i think he's like i wanna go
so you know try and support you know a guy
hey is neil maybe i don't either i know that that
so like why did i find highly love it was really rent my it'll go
hi my name's jeff
right oh well yeah well see that sunny right like hey
see avenues thing okay let's say
but i see your point pretty cause you to panic
you
in that way now i got a lot going on about
people around them but
to know how to type broken i like for me
no no i'm retired letter that let's say i know i was there that one out of the earth that yeah probably
hey i can tell there right now
yeah right but even when you play with it you know
marriage
yeah well
yeah where where do you guys said what what was the other hand
right they live for me what town
yup i couldn't live on that but so
oh my god we'll see
no no
that one
but yeah i love you know
really
yeah i was saying
that's fine now
let him know all time or whatever
right
oh wow