hi i'm hi hi what's that
oh i mean jokes can i hear jokes clean the sex thinking that banana his knock nap who's then then since then and then i can anna his neck not who's this the gas bananas not cat who's uh managed to put an who who's uh
manhattan now mack whose name manny not me
maybe in a banana his who who's there but then who who's a nanny for then who our cat who's a banana who who's there
i'm from who
you've trained trained them and
yeah isn't good joe hi hi hi you have a joke you want to tell
not to say i never been out of his not his thing and honest banana
mm tonight is there apple too
you're exposed like love i love you
care siamese
not oh then but i