mm mm
and um
got to be a good deal i mean a paper on the news right i got to lay in my
the real they then in the brand name and then um
but then during the day today
be around and then they go down the road but
but then then they they
you the the
do you
the the young then again they they've done and they don't make any money back
and then
yeah going down about uh uh i'm in um yard yesterday died the uh in the are you interested at all the ones on a job comes down to a job strategize the live down by the time then they follow up on the the the and then the young di di di di di di da da da da da and then the going to i'm a big backed by now and uh you know
and uh
better job by law say marriage i can live on
well you know and and and and and and
you can get and then when my father i mean you know the a bra
and and be
and and and and and and uh
and i've been waiting so long to go a long time
well uh
and and and and and china and you and um
no
and then and then
been so long ago and uh
uh
and then and then bad thing