day number four hundred and fifty five expedition watch too many members of our team
the core members shelf hi
i'm trying to count in my head right now i tell you how many days i've actually been here and how many weeks i i kinda lost the tough times because we started going back to school or going to really because when i first came like ten days ago she didn't want to go to college i'm working learning english and then we've gone through three different builders they kinda given up the frustrating part right now not knowing how long things are going to take and wanting them to hurry up wanting to do a good job and have the house stand when we leave
for the um
uh i'm like i'm just lot
the heart is in boy for the businesses
i'm going on and the read turn a corner thinking about
uh last time we were going to move in your not on that one gets to the doctor's fees on the news now they're just coming after them not a
yeah
no no no no no
uh no no no no no problem with that
you