they said you in the fifties
cake for speaking by lightning totally bottom cooking spray or you shorten so you can get okay and
maybe about twenty four so you only have two little ones
and then the liners small cat know the small cabinet those little shell and we can do that
pick up the liners you have
right you don't leave town gets off the
one thing
okay what are you know open and put it in the bowl
you gotta measure out what it says in there about three i think it's you might to want use the scissors or don't worry that everywhere we you might wanna check it out of
are there any illnesses or does like i said yeah what do we do now food and i don't know why they have another time well i guess
so you haven't done it completely it though you might want to do it all the first time and decide if you like
make a bigger home all the way across the top yeah um
and red and white what we're doing okay um what else
well one cup of water and we
right
she gets a little bit of landscaping until makes you are low speed for two minutes wait or with my i need one there's one stereotypical
no
i think the after she do that i i live in alaska yeah you know putting your mode you're gonna foreign trade or yes i think that's why we got show with wait a minute he'll get it out with the sun pick you out were censored
i don't know she knows she knows i'm
mhm
a video camera for his birthday okay he's almost three will they won't show
so when you're ready or i try not to get any more
mhm
oh lord have mercy
nope
okay let me think i know you have to put the bowl and put them in there and then you got to walk it in turn the bowl or right turn it towards the duck all right yeah i noticed one notch
for just like that one of the time i was i wanted to i want any day now says so lonely let it they say oh
well if you can't hang on here we mix to well first take this thing now that later
it's not about about making cupcakes
they just
mhm
oh my gosh you can't put this back in there now here we're on calls during the
and then you'll know wash your hands i loved it
yeah see i have some will have you know
slip this down wash your hands when we get a new towel after you wash your hands put it down we'll wash your hands i hate sports washing hands with another
the dirty washed up on it put it in the laundry room there's a lot to remember that cooking now wash your hands and face let me see your face yeah wash your hands so did you take that yeah
well off of their term grab that handle it all and now you can hold it was a handle and into the ones
mhm
like that
well for about two hours
that's so funny
i i can't you can't i just don't don't watch that i'll get it later yeah see i don't know i think you'll like his mom
i'm six years old you're forty or a man
okay i told i don't like that new one he wanted any
mhm
whole lie well i don't think they're going to want to do you gotta you gotta get the age
yeah
and then then then then then then we can explain like dot com
maybe
no
true