no
no no no no no they are kind of lay down and then i know
uh-huh
the
they don't search and now that um
i don't know how
so a little
and uh and and
nice
ah tell them that way i i saw um nine eleven i know why tell me on one i i i'm not making money on
uh
no no no
mhm
and see
i'm talking about people who make yeah when was it like i mean i'm i'm i'm thinking that if i was on oh it's on my day
yeah
uh
they want to the on a plane i'm studying
no no no no
and no i'm i'm a
no
you know they may not and
i uh just know a and my
yeah it wasn't as good as far as i got that's like telling me that that got accounting i mean people are saying that they thought that was the one i got my
no way a lot i don't know that um
and then
i went through the
and on my house and i was on a number and said oh no not now i and i and live a welfare and uh
and ah