and i
trying to sell food on top of all the holidays i think the only time like to watch your own kind of like a a guy
i'm
on our uh longer around um
and uh and and and i don't know
you know
i don't know
they they they they they bang bang bang bang bang bang and and all that and and and ball bang bang bang bang
no hold them like they do in texas they told me that baby when they when they done that one that is hard
and in in
no we don't no no no no
bunk bunk they want to know what we will be on and it bothers me that much of it now
and she
no no every day you know about you know get married again
or
mom other than your you know the don't think i'll pay you um
no i love her
no no no
no
yeah what i was reading some some milk because we don't smoke don't try to go out but me about your least absolute i'm just trying to think about all the dogs don't need to do today but normally say can you make it so i'm just going by do doors you know you you know
uh my my my and you know
and
no
how long ago um dream on a a a and a lot longer than that and um
uh
and the bible and