right yeah you must think we still you know like wasn't paying attention you know
thank i started you know tables joke about the come down and got my life not really a lot
it's a thousand something
family family uh i learned how to play
actually i don't know how to play with the um the um electronic you know years ago when he first came out and i'm like playing it taught me you know and then i started going to i play like my days off or before work being lower on the plane you know for our two hours you know and uh you know playing that one
yes
you can take like a person's personal you know
you know or
so uh that's what makes it so as a legal like real people and so it's like a skill to do it you can just sort of skill
yeah you're right
we've got we've got
yeah yeah sure man