sounds like are you making are you oh my gosh humid perfect star man yeah
i'm so you don't have to stand still buy yourself show me put it over here um
perfect so daddy how you can
age for being making cookies for santa gotta watch out because the tricky part the rolling it's a tricky part it's not easy mommy was having trouble we had to put 'em in the fridge to cooling down because they weren't willing to stick
that's okay just those those watches her daughter
per se daddy can you hold on to this law i guess one of the oven and that's good
start a gingerbread man a tree we're gonna decorate them
you can do the cooking
yeah
are getting a little sometimes it gets stuck on here and you have to periodically cleared up
and then put fresh
well it's gonna be very excited or you go girl
so
perfect christmas tree
jeeze
okay