well
well uh
mm mm
mm
uh
from the new greenhouse we sitting in the greenhouse we've japanese cars is chris and that's about the moment just see what happens very cloudy day today outside the temperatures nineteen degrees three which is uh not too bad yeah so i just a few to a a supply and things and helping with the work to for the the big screws and the tips i never today's lovely i never to the dog
mhm
let me think anyone knows
connie uh that was to for me to do alone designer thing
mhm
so everyone who watched it on youtube followed progressive the especially uh
i don't want to do i have to think of a new project
well this is signing off from the greenhouse
a good