and uh and and and and
nah
nice talking to out there like they they i think i i don't know whatever
okay do you control them free soda you know your hips or senator right on this really see it but i really easy for me just relax okay looking at us the people in his for you right now
no what is going to say if you don't see a lot of people very similar to what they they just unisom okay legs soda pop straight up twenty backwards okay sometimes that sounds good um it's a cool most liberal freon free bike looking foolish okay just want you to push down on the type of that which is good for a second hands moving okay good good keep your hands most nickel tend to slide down a slug is if you want to say the well as we can is this an obstetrician hold on
whoa whoa whoa whoa
i'm not going to be down the drain gum in track
you know i don't know that she wanted that gland that ran a that i go back and i'm from and
neither can play in
they asked about i don't know what i was thrown into the doctor that gland and that back a a and a canada and um
what about the track when i go no no no it's not as much
you know i i know that's pretty much read the headlines on our land and that way but i don't go out and and and
were you on a brand new bathroom mayor which bad man going john been a while to new a volvo bounced around bottles are you going to then lab the matinee
the same thing i learned some movies that are going to lay on the other day a
uh all the great life with them my latest bashing bowl i'm not i mean you know what i'm saying they live in santa monica and jane
well i'm in new me dr dr i'm in and some movies are good blame on the
what was going to run