uh today is a guy that i knew uh by the way and i'm not very selfish reasons for going swimming for me to go on the and uh a machine
i just saw the beginning and again i don't know helped me
uh for me like a big thing and uh russia actually i'm here in um uh
yeah i'm on the brake monitor three
and uh uh british or underground that kind of um yeah may start to being associated with there are also a problem with saddam hussein it just seems that when the research that i'm i'm a a a social security and uh
the plot release favorite barbecue and um
and a lot of revenue in really do
yeah i'll put labels on the kitchen yeah i'm also i'm in my
or did you have to come to light and i'm really not too
yeah well the nail on that yeah and they have like you're on a machine like my other line
and uh which is like a d._j.
i'm located now don't you know