it's always been one of his
it'd be like oh what's good too
hi patty hi okay middle man
finally it doesn't to change me sick working
that's fine if you just aren't ya
you're you hear a wrong
wow oh yeah well yeah you gotta get from pennsylvania
well it sounds pretty good anywhere around lauren
yeah it's coming right there yeah oh mean right into the building there on the end
no way i don't know that there a swim around
random heroine right right
so what are those i mean i'm in love with it hey by the way i'm looking at the right way
right
you guys number kidding man syria terrorists
my other line shocking to me it's getting her right the what
they just
live there are thrown unbelievable the very right
no i like randy how somebody else right there and they're like own little uh sorry i don't know to swim so crazy
they are they care i don't know more more than i think whatever you to want
parents to be on the ground like its point i thought well you know instead of them
yeah i can come in here me outlaw um
okay now it's like that is boring you and she was working
and i'm gonna go need a little one in my oh i know how
oh
well you know i've learned that wise right now i'm so yeah
well the screen you know they were or
some of the building oh i'm okay
pardon oh give it up again oh am i grow up
oh way i've been to go shopping
right there in any way yard and
you know ready to go to happy i'm gonna laugh at themselves for
oh lord you know i mean yeah you got the channels
you weren't god oh boy well my number the most committee elsewhere yeah he's uh like now what up
oh these three in the name of it i know there's a car rides verna i haven't seen them man that's not it's like night and he wanted them
oh i see them really is unbiased drinking right
i'm probably tackling hard named hans alligator was the of guys yeah really and
dry here it's rising that y'all um
i would not want to have wanted to talk on the roof for that i'm glad i'm not really
yeah and sometimes they aren't really settled i said not worth it
up here in troy doggy on uh yeah yeah oh oh
friends today i mean yesterday the motel like you know okay let's go this way
hi
what kind of cameras any thing
hi this is right on that kind of on the
hello hey i'm i'm like look at that hour like line no not yet other why
and then transformers oh my god
i rarely home land and now yeah mainly hell now he's gang
are going on man
okay yeah we just we just got really like came on i think you're right now
you know no i don't know how hard at home
how there right now we're going to go anywhere you called me about ten minutes the heat
they call all these people sitting out
yeah yeah
you know what we don't have the you know how many people you know trees and
to being up it poor dog yeah
down theory on that often down there like
yeah and i think i think i'm black walls and then you won't be able to go on the way back down again they might not the house
so no get like the marine blowing up all his part about how you're gonna true oh
that's really
and you can see the power line as well
how are you are yeah yeah hey see um may have here
canada iran she doesn't foster
yeah that that plane can imagine uh bigoted or what have you ever see like you know but i of ever seen one wow this is close enough