what was the teacher said today
see
i'm on my own business trying to make movies and this is what i get interruptions i was i want
okay so we have three cape may seem to be a moose abroad and the ball more torso should go on the table and try to make that we see that this is a big influence you can do for you okay
mhm
alright his legs now working working on the wrist
so we're cutting any beep that's about it hopefully they give us some years
i think it's safe to say that god made me to video work the bakery that we've got so far
about ice hordes that'd be fun not really because now we do this what we do
well for for this way that's what we're trying to do that's what we did this is my first by the way you experience yeah a nuclear doing that you know set up a table so i was from anything anyway okay okay do you need any resembles grey hound out i was just oh man
a race is dolly i think yeah too much to drink before so
yeah good
correction you're trying to lose and i got to win women raise your hand cut something i just what i mean it's
yes my back you at or are you in a the he of the better i didn't eat that yes she did freaking fought for the better and then started distributed between her kids a lot because i hardly have a place we had plenty happy birthday