and then then then but then
and then
and and and other times where she knows exposure herbs exposure to understand
and there's times where he knows the times this just don't
pretend special times she knows the times and the times change the explosion the times
special and then there's the times national person
deneen bowling depends actions
but then as she as she started studying just depends oceans
especially in the ocean
depends depends depends actions the penn study and then as you can just studying
oh she just she just she just she just
special dependence independence stations depend depend
special
studying independence
special depend depend specialist
well especially in this depends depends depends depends oceans interest thing especially and
studying the things that she
special special special interest
yeah mhm
and ah she knows better and uh
and uh
and er and er
and then and times times that