the the the lady ladies in the morning
they
then they'll say oh no
um but then again they want to know why they got the the way they thought that dedicated to my mom said with the methadone that you know that you the quality
like they do get to meet you how long we we were happy and you can't see when we go out and buy it that'd be interesting to see that you know stop the the the job when we found everything and the know what do you think to the side will be censored
they don't mind me and my dad and she had no no no go back and we will do but
yeah do the sauce and they you know they say the same you're really really uh
uh say they say they got all your that
i'll buy them in the whole leg trouble but your right hand it to come out come in we live in the right then and then about eighty eighty eighty eighty to come up to the job he jumped that that you know you know you know go wrong with the rate we're going to iraq and iran and iraq and iran go through because they gotta they gotta they gotta you gotta bumped around i gotta go about it
yeah yeah we go again say they do the men get their boat it don't get the job on the boat to get their boat
no they nobody gets lonely time to me