gee
that also had them betty hey what's your first call waiting all day on you
well actually i'm really though well wow that that little hi oh bet that cleaning
bike demos constantly although here's one you get this last week on ya yes washington new it'd be with uh
oh man
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh to keep
right
oh god no not but on that yeah okay
oh no oh god no like nah nah
oh oh syrians oh bug cheated nah nah
yeah
i think it was offensive to okay you don't you don't you them just you know i like
oh well she wasn't up and that's about the dogs don't didn't even visit that okay
yeah yeah button you bought something
oh you're muslim
well you know they just got gotta do not i'll you've you've got called yesterday but he has set up
oh yeah oh yeah oh gosh yeah oh yeah oh god
oh yeah oh sure oh yeah oh yeah oh i know oh yes oh come by now because the dog yeah oh god