oh i see like a i mean in the atmosphere i go into the atmosphere roll around me surrounded by
you
they're not even a climbing wall never tried down what i do uh well one day we'll be out of school and uh they can't be it won't be
that's nice
so surprised by the way they look at me and then in the now looking at the fact that i'm on the back or don't want to be threat now school got a couple of
you keep too
if money born right by the time when
chemistry they can't even find a man he yells blown up i was growing up but uh seem to be
it's got us in this in this world
yes i agree there
but uh you know i got my own pace you know racist people around me is they complacent but i can't stand the same
some drums and it's scary to be
barely even with a team they don't really understand the man
i'm trying to uh to be slow down and the cost of my life
uh this is going or something