and she into the pentagon got mad then she from the pentagon she
and then maybe i might add done a
and and ah
a little around that age here
yeah you gotta time uh
um and and
right
um
um and
and
a lady and the idea and and i mean she i say you know my age and day out today
going to hang out and she
any shining and and i don't know and and and doing signing on it and
little down in tennessee and what about nine and and they're on t._v. and and so
and then i'm not saying now
and and the cat is many animals mountain dew
and on and
and and yeah and
label
hey who knows
yeah well hey hey hey hey who got loud
any any
and um
and
and money and the other day and uh
yeah
er