and um
occupied non-issue brings you gotta have a baby about the sun shot it is a little bit on like your god and they
i mean
no when was your last last night when when not dumb one second to last like the the medicine we chat with the the most popular name on a lot a lot of fun to go for walks with more on the she was only two
i bet you do
that's going to the and the let's go through the mail box and then by by the shop and i don't like you know how the
a lot
that was no way we go
really good yeah
yeah right oh i i'm convinced
you know
oh yeah uh certainly not
yeah
i'm not sure what i'm saying
but
and um they bought the car she put me on the shopping and the cold
i go talk to me you know not in the back down and talk about what's going to jump right on the border not that good know you know who don't want to be something that the the pet that active
well she ended up above the
and the the time leave you know people can be in the late by the time because they're not tell you what what they tell you
yeah he was with the all the time
and and i don't know and then they'll go and then they turn it on the other day and i don't know that