well you don't feel a for the and i don't see the
she is also a lot of them at
hello
well that's out again onto the superbowl they when you show a lot of our have you didn't get to federal set but i don't
but i'm going to keep it on on so a lot of the a a
i'm getting all this
there's
what i mean been
she she is yeah that's nice
you know uh
i i looked at you
i know that
okay
what else to we well that's that's the the
she think that you can you tell me
let's way through because it's
did you get
to me the common fool uh you don't have a governmental from two eight records that is what i don't know that's that's okay i get through this year
the from what i mean i
just to talk to somebody like we to go to settle down here will
or or you know this you know well we have to worry too much to say they get to see that you know