yeah so are you are but i didn't work out to get on
what are yours slicker
what you think the whole the smaller us ken
project a little a little dog alright these chicken eugene
well i can
they don't make it really says that when they were saying
try to garden well i'm not gonna do it but i don't care what oh nice oh nine himself to walk into the tournament do not do it
he didn't tell me that you were married yet
hello
anyway i knew hotter weather system we're not going to estimate it so um
at that your hands knew how to make but that's okay well so uh see once you got one time maybe
about that um
yeah i tend to foreigners long hair
whoa whoa starbucks
what did you say but i'll be i'd say
it was four inches from near and dear oh what is really about forty miles
from this thing and also really tiny tiny highway builders
free anything i to make fun of me about my tiny i always got away courthouse you go away i don't want to get an adequate words the first i got one
right right yeah i mean i i think i would win on now