mhm
mm
mm mm mm
i'm not a good well then we buy other shows know we know she remember same
mm
means let's see
and she had to throw them soon then they do
no
that's a dream you mean them for those things she's crazy but in a for
hum
and she swears that she
she had to her and she says she
god and
uh uh and and i'm sorry say good bye
and um
me too
the last time you know to grave she'd been given in a small town where she's going to be blown machine a lawsuit dreams
may not do the job
and then they're paying me didn't know not to do that you me and me
oh they did some things that have been
no
maybe
oh
right
no
ah no
thanks
they do a day to day basis and
the damn every now and i'm sorry oh
you know um
and i'm i'm sorry
uh uh a uh
no
mhm