do the best way to prevent
use the places to provide you started on the edge between the top covering the metal case gently pry open the case five tabs on each side on the bottom you need to be released in order for the metal kids to be device
really open to to to have
mhm
short ribbon cable connected to small circuit board
must be unplugged from the headphones circuit board use the plastic to provide that to fry the cable
on the edge still find cable and i've
really
mhm
lift up the hard drive to get access to the battery
using the two screws holding down the logical
no
carefully lift a lot of people here they better free cable from under the boards
jeopardy probably up on the battery to release it from the case may be attached the case double sided
in the middle east
place the battery in the case same orientation which the original was
lift the logic forward and run the wires underneath it
okay
reposition screws down to the case
in the middle east
the battery cable back into it
just drive back on the case that's connected to the small circular
and then you can to to have the device
he
the