mhm nice what insurance was showing a thousand phone doesn't exercise exercise
did you
at the beginning exercise on practiced a little open
good
in a
they can fill in exercise
when they show i'm
within you know and you can just like the and
mhm
she just
exercise
usually done was amazing
that's true
shoes or
teach him progression
things naturally the c- the hope that the students
funny that you know
mhm
among my she will be interesting
nice to each other the other stuff
mhm
well that's not to
during that he's only two or three inches
mhm
that's right that's right it's gradually
would be funny without
mhm mhm how often next to me that
yeah
she she
in michigan
he's holding in tennessee direction connection to work you know
running to the left hand you know the vikings
no
my my chance huh
about two to three seconds
some of the gym
in front of the gym
so this year shelving gradually pushed ahead with respect to see them with for about two three at least hopefully these incentive but you
down to to um
straight angle between that thirty degree strangely enough the whole money up with her to teach them
had that too
immediately the hopefully hand inside the gym
diagonally about eighty degrees
just the standard time really
she wanted to change in the back of the
pretty much the whole wish they had like just try to just
mhm
school
i live um
when the authors and actually had a hot that
23 thinking at least the whole thing
none
the the main as as in an area
you know how much did you think the last three centimeters one person she