everybody welcome to uh my new math book silver addition uh on boxing here i am driving up to a productions which is where my son works they were able to buy my book and uh since i'm a non profit church he takes his boss willing to have it for a in a very kind to let us or to get the apple slight discount we can't say that
do that for anybody else but he here at the productions which is
i got my uh and i'm i'm in johnson's office now opening up a favorite alright go ahead and i said i said a
the are really very very light only weighs about four and a half a pound or is made of a solid block of aluminum has a keys which takes a little bit of getting used to
and from watching so many of these on boxing i know this is a cab
pull up the computer comes out
very nice i did have to wait for uh probably three weeks or so in order to able to get the computers
but this is pretty cool
spend a lot of my time watching other people open books on you
it's really quite a bit to get all that wrapping off but at least you knew that were going to be any friends on it
everything is amazingly san diego
ooh
a shiny three
really looking forward to being able to use the ministry as you can see we we do a lot of video bible studies and it just is pretty tough to do my five year old pc hopefully this'll save me some time
so now i'm on the uh bible videos we do every day will be done right on here