taylor mountains here there's a lot of hard work and dedication to be able to do something like that he's wonderful people here with us today take the challenge like everybody's running around and we're looking like like
did do
that you guys usually totally what is this somebody lost focus and i mean
i just beat it
fair share
yeah i live
to the to them it's very tough climb however the reward is great hardest feeding feel like i'm
that that that's great
no for country wants to beginning of my car everybody's running around and or or looking like to talk about around here is about the bar
uh we're almost
and the guy came in and i mean