mhm
boy this uh
and they will and they can see that
my name is they don't they they they had been a many and what they do
but in the middle east and they came back in may and i'm a downfall
do you get there but they didn't mention it and think you know down the hill
they did in your and buy things that i'm not happy about it and my my dog she was saying how
or what ever and
they had me sign something
that is
i've heard people say that much of anything good for your but i don't know has we love we love it made the to me like it's just not enough
um and then there are so big i'm i'm planning on uh if you don't know what i'm saying or whatever you do your kids go all the time they're they're i'm going to be paying a gang up on the other way round ligament pain and you are only a bad way and i mean you your carry to man i'm telling you about the same old thing every time you did say i'm a big you know i don't know i don't know i don't know about a bank or no i can't get a lot
john
they they are you do my favorite kind of shady limit they they say well you are you running shade a baby with the baby a day to day every other word is okay to do it to the time not around what don't you think the same way
you know i mean do do they mean learning in maryland where are you feeling
do you like when my please don't to change the amount that you just got in the house it's hard to believe that you are at home but the point of being in pain when you say
they told me that we don't want to learn the language
yeah you get your girls
to preschool they go away
i know do you do you know they they go in there
mhm
no