no for excuse me
yeah
you know
um but my back they're open she looks you
gee
who
yeah
everybody
yeah for something else okay here can i i i thought oh
i can't just go out you know she you know better i can't fit in without driving
right
hello
whoa
go go go go
nope
what's your washing bush
no closer go
okay
yeah
everybody over
so we
you get your grandparents
that's my plan
isn't it grilling turning the giants
uh not a giant tree i know you can't play very well yes
what did she weigh when you sit down
cool
there was something to what are you doing and what are you doing haven't haven't really
that's true that's true
what are you doing yeah i didn't
way too lazy well
they get lazy
to drive a car