mhm
huh go ahead and okay wow currently ninety
um i lap
hockey hockey i mean i think it oh you're probably
for sure journals collie
yeah there's kids make race
yeah
um so i'm trying to also i'm i'm i'll
fine they have um okay karen i'm twenty two
things things and learning daddy frankie baby
me okay
oh well okay well i'm a little worse
why not last to keep on he was saying that
like because like i think tea thinking i'm doing
oh really
flying flying kind sighing sighing and he banning
u._s. wish oh
i'm sure it's really paid right i mean
and it to me no way late sites
i um
they had the same time
um somewhere
john things young thing i'm
oh i right um
well green