oh
really
a saturday and sunday
yes
no
oh oh mom
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa
new i'm like oh man
and in the world and
no
yeah
oh
uh i
or
or or or
i know and i'm like man i don't know
no
you know they say that
ah that one day
yes
okay
no
every day
i know all over well no no
then
okay
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
or or you know
well
wow
what
um i only watch the the average wage carry a bar or otherwise
no
okay
you know i'm older or or
sure
a day
um
no no no oh okay oh the the
so
you know
why why why what
whoa whoa whoa
no
oh and
no no
i mean no no oh
you know
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
no
oh man
oh really
well i don't like it why are they doing well in band and uh
no
healthy
or
oh ho oh
no
oh no no no no no
yea
why
no
mom's mom or the world why am i am day
what
and they are
yeah
okay
we're we're we're
so we will see me in the whole new
going to do
and
no no you know some people who are running
so uh where you're are longer longer
no
the way it is a lot of
yea i am a you know
no
anyway
man
no
are you
ooh
right but you know
whoa
no
some day
whoa whoa whoa
ooh
no
you can just shit
where are you
oh no
no
then
when was
yeah
why
all the other phone
and do it
man
yeah
why why
the thing
okay
no
you know
yeah
okay
alright
whoa
no
i no no i don't know
yeah
you know i'm home alone
no no no no
know
well i don't know
yeah he told me about it
okay
we're in the last game that we got so much
that's why
on all day while i was on a day
whoa
oh
yeah
no
that way
so i don't know
okay it's a long way away
oh cool
hey hey hey hey a a a a
i don't know anything
no
okay
i'm in boston for outdoor or indoor
oh okay
no
oh i'm you're like actively
who
okay
i don't know why why why don't from there
oh
am
okay
taste you know or oh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
no no no no
no no no no no no no i don't know why why
mom or oh
well i was going on one last night
new
no
whoa
it's a little too away
no me neither
okay
hey
no no no no
oh
no
mhm