and the
your dishwasher door doesn't look correctly machine itself one town on there's a and the dog mechanism so that one come on the when doors open this video unless you have to replace the dog mechanism on the couch point dishwasher nice to bill won't even open correctly be a problem with the and you can send me another video replacing the hinges on this dishwasher show you and before you do any work i'm going to stop by removing the screws along with
so
okay so now i able to slide out this fight just be careful what they said hey it's incredibly sharp you cut yourself very easily to give us a little bit more into work
you can see the just two screws holding it in place some of those
the removed and we put the new mechanism fucking exactly the same light
and then no i'm just because of the shell patch now i just need to replace the screws along with
let me tell you how to replace the couch for this we're gonna to take off the top flight just need to remove two screws should just lift off so we just need to remove this
hold on
on the couch should just come away from the catch quite okay
for the new one on
so we have any catch catch place
so we got a new dog replaced on the whole point dishwasher bulldoze i'm trying