they've been doing less some of the sunday yeah it's we're leaving leaving you guys all that cashiers some
no i'm actually i like the lead on and off the gross
very funny
oh my god down
um hi jake here today singer police
i'm down i'm healthy you know you're down who else is down in jail i read some
before you wrestling again like i was so upset but some people smoking fuck is taken that much
you gotta look into his job man wrestling are you kidding there then we read even today many frame venue
last allen what else is going
are me out about that day that's why you gotta play it
prior when i run the body shit i can feel for them
so you got wife shit i'm amy
really i don't really want to do this do hey yeah man i'm glad to be here to visit us right yeah i feel much shit to slam huh
five flights are robbed we've enron
much revving sounds or leaving here soon i got an arcade
you got three give me good die from five fifty cents
sorry on score ticketing home
i guess huh cool right
that's funny my let it in a fear
no rifle tries to do that uh
plus i'm sorry what
'cause those are both
through on the ground
yeah
oh cool oh
yeah for rowing studying left in the back of tricky rubber was done
and what is your opinion no sorry
frightening lower wants to four
thinks that here man what was that nobody was like a block on those before um
i didn't do handstands and then with 'em off into the air with your friend
well you're still standing on one hand yeah
you tap with your hands who is living in them
don't solve is
slap dropping they're just so much blood in his head ready to have
really mean you can get 'em all fitness
oh brother
oh oh oh oh oh man
that little movie did aerobics the
i can't really remember are you married what was that doesn't play in the central time and got the other line take the book and the agility of a man
but it's a nice hats short lived there you get off of the signs
that far sorry about that before you get good cracking
you ought to hold them that's okay
and here i gotta i gotta you gotta leave leaving iraq going home
so we have a freeway wrestling match sex or somebody
so do you have the ground british over