you're actually get more
and then you're on um pretty much on candid camera
because i have to focus manually inside exposure manually one um
taking a video oh your team video yeah you were like
you know change the uh u._n. everything and we were telling you
i went home still no accounting or some actor you no i don't know um
okay okay i'm not a camera you when i eat 'em on a
i read money i guess if i had no more mommy
terrible terrible i think the worst joke they've ever heard
and then he'd be real bad sort of feel
you can't miss at a mom a b. shootings you sound island
this thing slow you don't get you know and i vote it's korean i don't remember what it is but it's very good
yeah i eat out also
yeah