mhm been living in the beginning and then
mm how many women when they were going to do
my dogs down on line and then during the war going on in the in the union yeah i guess they would know careful yeah i guess they mean to me
on their uh um we i out there in your ah
no no no no or you know who knows maybe we can be a day to be
you know man you're not the the or the city i being a gall bladder your answering the
have read i read the common man oh man she ah died
no no no no no no not really playing on the other day
start a band saw actually she is there any uh
mhm
no no no no so they can see you know the players
no no no man i mean no no no no and i can see what you're saying is saying and they're going to be a good day
and then
mm