mm mm mm mm
mm mm
no
ooh
and and we live in
mm mm the oil out on long island the uh
and uh um uh or or whatever and and and or or
mm i'm a a i'm i'm a in uh
you do do do do it now they say say i i know
i i do
yes they do they do
i don't know it's awful and i already ready to go because i know the whole we read i read a little more
so i mean i
you know i'm ready i'm ready for the rent and ready go
i do that you use it i thing
how old are you ready for going on and tell me anything you know i'm ready to go now tell me your name
you too
it has to be for the day it
in in in the news and then when you're in the long way one and it should be a good time but they wanted us to the time and um they wanted to do during the day is a great while do you guys you say
yeah sometimes the rain you know the the children my lifestyle and your wife has a lot of the same kind of a a a general well uh why my mother and a lot of the the way
know