i've always than girls they were going to make a yeah i believe it or not all the upper am shut the stomach and oatmeal and some other spices and that's what we have here really good online place to get anything from overseas they they actually make themselves but it's like like this come frozen real nice because when i get around here so it's the easiest to way go to the cameras foods are on the web and shipping too yeah they actually just about anything you could possibly want from over there real easy um this is real simple to make to cook when you have a when i went through the process of making these like i said finding some of that stuff just for easy before and i didn't like it so uh in this part here when i have is some water and one you can do this but i just don't have the heart grow up with that much so um got some water and the you bring this up to a boil boy lives because if you boil it's gonna break the whining and that's bad you just want similar but let it simmer down puts us in their forty minutes done a lot more than we are going to um do some meats which are just a for and then some ah some potatoes with ups and potatoes and i'm i'm also that's usually the way you do it or not with this is gonna be the the so i'm gonna bring up to boil put this in their let it simmer for forty minutes i'll be done about thirty minutes throughout the twenty five minutes twenty minutes or so or put on the the turnips and the potatoes and let this be cooped up in doing that so we'll be back and just minutes
right my liquid here is uh up to an extent actually came to a football back to a certain level and he was er i guess we're going to uh put that in there while this is going to be approaching here i've got some potatoes washed and get ready because it just like i need to hear that a and we'll we'll all these together here in ah we'll get those the nice thing about fifteen minutes the potatoes for about twenty and i'm going to take forty so i want to get everything ready five minutes before i guess so we can get time to to match us up and um so we're gonna be my limits
alright and spend fifteen minutes since our uh has been doing here so it's gonna take twenty minutes to get the uh the potatoes then at fifteen minutes or so for the back there so i've got to make the uh potatoes on the twenty minutes cooked tender that we can smash those needs to take fifteen minutes so um we actually turn those on five minutes after so the dog down the same time anyhow will be back and you can see we're still blown away here the i guess is a pretty good clip about um ten minutes or so and the potatoes and then will be done needs needs you want to say i'm about five minutes to get those finished up around that time the hassle we don't play up in a back alright here we are we're i'm done cooking guess we're just looking pretty good really good some mashed potatoes actually made chicken stock
butter salt pepper um
i actually hit these with a little bit of of guinness beer which is why the brown but it's still just makes not quite the original way to make them
but you know what kind of be creative every once in awhile so to serve this up um here's how i'm gonna do it
start with a uh
nice dollar pair of
mhm
that my
and just afraid
pretty good i love mhm good
pretty darn good it's got some great flavors
nothing like you would expect it to but it's good try and one's in your life um i like that whenever i get a chance to just because it's it's good to me i think it's respectful to the animals to uh whatever we can but anyhow for me another beer and uh have some dinner