okay that's good it's a deal
learning and you have and i remember from my mom oh no
yeah uh-huh thought yeah he was on go on
funny yeah when they got to buy them on the highway
and they know they're going hey i learned the sexy mom i go
over there right there in front of them and say go ahead
i tell ya i mean that's me too is you think the camera
going to i thought i'm under another one i yeah i don't know what to try
oh it was nice janet they recording little man
no and it just i yeah wow yeah i'm just like they make their goal not come on
this is
we don't get no go ahead i'm already recording is on the phone come on
how do they tell you it's good
we can
my head hurts