yeah she's the hurt fetching though there
solid heightened inching
what else was japan maybe but like other yet okay features glory
yeah more one on more audio community you've done this before right yeah you kind of an emergency or put this off
i guess with their whole taste in need a when you put that on top of the super down there good morning patch or
you're that you hear all those things that that the stuff you're saying that it was a sign that moves dying from john from houston
i don't know we have to admit when the mother
um
what is happening other than yeah when i was going to put on and then they're just
no i haven't actually dogs when they're thirty you i i see
i'm a buddy who yeah it's all that money yeah let's stick with x. games on my list of it
i already got it the other room where you have to put it till you're not big or something about you know now they they'll maybe they'll have to say
a live next b. six or like things that problem and plus you're on
yeah i i mean gardening grass like hello yeah
i'm kind of jail so but
my friends yeah local go number on the topic i'm now you didn't really watering them a little bit yeah
mm mm
uh-huh
store oh what was going to go on strike
but my girl in there
yeah is what we have like no luckily inside over their high school would you part of the year me now
like written on their side boarding near fainted
really run into that like sophomores warning me find reliable
scar monday morning at my oldest one thing