things
oh interesting what do you oh
you got to curb plus you've got to my sold what might happen
hi tom strong on it all on my patio biting you could show
had been to say oh i know my son and maids 'cause actually i didn't say that
pretty good plus i mean it's a must mother been upon make just threatened in lansing mama anything
me for me to take
man wait i'll say in that accent insane
mine's i i'm from south by only uh
on earth in everything paying hand
and kill their lungs
they're dying is uh tape till they bad uh
well not as young i've ever been to adults and everything was young and my dad lived named pilots david and
uh you know bad uh any john chancellor who me
um just ill from there and it's yeah
absolutely
yeah that's that's not really joe the trial
anything that makes me anything that um the threat
tend to go there
much faster for for the week
oh really my lie i'd love it tactics only apple pie
i'm sorry oh tango kill john
they were buying is uh what you got any team too but um
young mindy so young but named pods named buying them die you're good man he was young so i don't me
i'm jenny so young and they were just on and
me no damn and that's the damn on back joanne
but to change anything you wanted to blow though
definitely
i hear your baby things you've made your baby
no i'm on kill dammit substandard joan okay let's say popped there by ah settles then uh
young young woman maybe job but
diane taped shows then uh