oh they're just gonna thing it plan get out of my head i don't remember
so no memory and i don't remember i thing so when i'm feeling really down about my really in the
and and myself things kind of low to turn on the t._v. and watch my super sweet sixteen
okay at least i'm not like that
so i bring out the costs camping in mexico which isn't imperative in when jokes and you really interesting because here put in like a sect of people who like used
anything about them and you're trying to get out as much information as possible and since i'm at a practical basically we're all from out of state from like all over the country and
and the easiest thing
to learn english people should like associate characters with them about their state
i'm from colorado and then like oh you can allied mountains then no the release of the caribbean or drifts
no let me think texas either tense
i'm from colorado and i need judgements about people from california and all over the east and everything
so the one thing i've learned at my school we have all kinds of museums i don't know just
lots of liberal arts and all the kids are pretty smart and whenever i go to a party i've learned that psychology majors are really good at peer pressure
and they they know their stuff
to take a drink no non get no like it it tastes great not good
so that hold your life when you went know collateral father figure and western attendant holding your line no uh
and again oh so i got to experience the election on a liberal
campus wasn't between
buying a cane it was between osama and neater there was no mccain on my campus did you register did you registered have you brush or did you vote did you go did you both
were doing this
maybe dreamed politically apathetic ten minutes and like i'm sorry
okay so i i'm a little bit too liberal on some things were not
to get into that because i really like my face the shape it is
get punched in way on here but i
opinion down at an art school and it had got me into a lot of debates and i've learned a whole bunch of like political labels that i've never heard before like and our go send the
little community sense ram a butcher in a bigger and risk it'd be like an r. t. but we're going to be organized and then i get really can i'm like i like
and i got paid they really got me i started thinking like what would it be like to live in a libertarian household like to grow up in one and the little baby like had walked me he can what where are crime you want to be said again you and your self self reliant dairy queens
so sometimes when i'm on yahoo
and i read my spanish it makes me feel really bad
so i'm like no i don't need to use car or to make money on craig's list or want to lose eighty five pounds of grown a date with the lana
i mean i think you
oh right back to college i go to an art school there are artsy guys
there which means i'm not afraid of being raped because i could beat up eighty five percent of that
i throw up and hearing your poetry
oh that's a nice song kind of reminds me jason rad
so why do you rent a type cancer to make him wherever dynamic or some circulation
probably i don't need a whistle
when i'm old and my kids are given me crap i'm just gonna pool when i was young used to be a plant
so they're just some phrases in life actually in movies not life that can only be okay in the context of the movie i e damn
until that happened um can you can not
other girl this time something to name again part in lion which seems to
brought up the lights a lot when who being chased by now and then she gets stuck in little branch election lurks hand
it's been i've been a scam okay so i wasn't ah
emotionally uh
is awesome because i especially going over my fear catching people are we going to be kind of a choice
yeah see you and even though i've got over my fear touching people i gained a fear of people with me
hot i think they booed and and showed you
my that i
not really comfortable i don't want to go with that says oh
so after semester
i think i just made the decision to drop out i found a new calling i'm mean
spontaneous turned the clinic really down the street from planned one where you have a bunch of mannequins cry their shoulder give you some teachers
my friends not a restaurant
into college wow
what do you college kids miss the most good fresh baked goods
oh we totally went down to safeway bought a whole bunch of the naturally total house chocolate lovers that kinda stuff
remember the labeled it's we've danger managed to have like the best time ever and ever like
genius we could sell these and make a profit or do it was awesome we get kids
take the four actor and dry or huck he went on rolling your little i got
and
dance we got our connections on mexico common knew
gosh
are getting basements feed that how is destructive it wasn't just an addiction affection area
listening to the bunkers have arm and you hear the knock of opportunity
and i just want to leave you all of that no thank you