what i'm also a fitness really was like no it's not that nice experience should stay long forms those skills gossip is like from so
some some of them because they're both in the it's it's just it's like
was it
okay and then um
probably some of them but um some of them
if they don't i thought you said the mother they know that i saw still know well they might or or mine those were my minor stuff i don't to know for the summer so i on
and they don't guy
what does that come out with them shows these action considering going on it's probably nothing from money you didn't celebrate christmas
um with all the owners though some interest in you know
someone else i don't think you know
or you know in a you know
a lot of guys from them you know there's always like
and then
it's like it's still
and some of the the some rooms though for them some of the in my in laws live
yeah they and then for some years ago
with the stuff to do