you know the guy going to go camping and you know none of them
one i got a fan of attention is monday night whereas my wife's family tries guys will be my mom now they're back down the middle east an accidental nowadays
and then they
well
they're going to in the water was ready to go
they are they
you can make
no
thirty dollars
mm mm
and then not going on around by the time on the back yard thailand right
no and how old are you down and then now eighteen months old she's big
my money and the baby
i was pregnant
by the way and cameras there and
john good garden you know i believe that that's right
what do you have
anybody can be
um
i don't know my back and i didn't know about
nah me and my mom
oh i agree with you being for the kids get to hear the heartbeat right
yeah
mhm
no no no