and last time i think and and now now now
uh the the the more danger
um don't last too long and blah blah blah blah blah blah not enough i why don't you know blah blah blah blah blah blah and then they mind the other now that are around the and they are not allergic to them now i go all the time or for
the only well you know you don't want to put down
so i don't i don't know i'm i don't know i'm not
and um and of them than the than than than than than the than the world and
oh there's always stuff to the old exactly what we're doing here in the several different putting all the all hammer dogs that i'm using now the one we found the most effective they feel would you not at all down technique good job okay thanks for beer
that was the last one i got over there i'm not
mm
and then i'm going to do with them than than than than than than than than than than than them boom and shit and boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom and shit and boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
when when that was a
when i'm alone di di di di di da di da da da
back da da da da da da da da friends and and uh i'm a guess fan i love them no
nah
and i'm just less than that i'm while i'm a little better
no
um