walking back for another exciting experiment this one is called color changing liquids i have my assistant
does he smoke and my
i think he's still here in front of us we have two cups filled with regular tap water in a little bit of what's called red cabbage juice powder that we've mixed in their previously in my system in both assistant
now we're going to take one scoop of baking soda
thank you and put it in one cup what the thing no no no no stir it up
i don't really the crazy isn't it
i'm trying to please stop starting with a strong plate scoop scoop the other one we can see the transformation he stood up little straw
ten our intake citric acid
just wants to and put it in the second cup pick sure uh
from the purpose mhm cool now now if we take a third cop no no no no no no no no no no listening and we're going to put a third of all i could turn red purple almost read a bit of this in here for blower for this one in here
oh it's my turn to purple okay or black we didn't do think enough the changing colors