you're going to know each day for us and then i'm gonna understand um going to blow you away
right now right into his own that we just building james governance so honestly i don't like the song and about i mean
and it's not on anything
things and party
and try to limit and on there you go
and then be a miracle as i remember only laid up
and then in the city and all and struggling and that kind of thing and they were interested in the snow they cleaned up in the mood and that and there was nobody wants
and he didn't mean to him in the family and raining
the baby and then the brain and i need to
well yeah i know the dorm and daddy and um
especially when and then you know
and all and all this going on to them
you know
oh no no they're hearing and nah you're calm
nah nah the bus
so anyway their um