okay
my mom no no no no no no no
my god
oh my mind your going by your mind
you my mind
you know my mind
no
my my my
was when got
i don't know anybody who
no
are they competing for something like when you're working together the anti competition competition
there she knows how to use it to work for people to work on getting a little over two
my father is so for say for all of us are able to be here and relatives perhaps they found i that day and we to you know i'm in the news the being you know was raised in on the computer she has with her hair every body night and the um more i hope that this is more to her that it and produce
food for her and her family anyone else they need more brown surrounding today was the last thing you um going to keep your eyes over it makes everyone here today and
no
and uh