yeah oh
i don't know oh i do
oh wow so um
oh i know
oh la la la la hola long day uh
oh i didn't know what i'm not a holiday
oh uh huh
oh yeah yeah oh no oh they're awesome
yeah plenty and um the oh i hear you
oh boy oh i'm doing that and i never knew that had um
and i
oh wow oh my love of the house um i don't care finished warmer right
here's what age they know about ohio tires and what
k._u. almighty dollar oh wow
and another baby oh yeah i want to listen to all honestly and oh man drawing bringing ohio or um
yeah it is it all on the uh
right and who you going to be more reading aloud to live and all on the lid on how you think they won all homeless or your
i heard one learn by you know
oh i met her kids oh
oh oh really
oh ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho
gotta a._o. although no oh my god
hello hello there even about oh
right right well no no no they all of our we go
no even know how many oh he asked me you know
well how do you know i really would be you know
oh okay you know uh oh yeah no oh how
hey well you know we're or more
yeah i like i and i we hardly be nine
all over my mom long we how long ago me more or
oh he oh oh oh oh wow oh boy
oh wow that so don't how long how long i uh um
yes if you oh you
oh oh me more on the the only
yeah i know who who who like oh no no no i know how
oh yeah oh i know he well hard on me
yeah and uh the whole world i know they don't follow logic oh wow
i i would die
that's what i mean even the a little while
oh really oh who where did you uh neil
and uh but uh
it is i mean girl or a lot of things
oh i love wise
wow
oh oh