mhm
rather getting on the machine bullet table
indian teenage credit sports i think that they will manage
missouri
mostly
max radio flier over to on them out of it
yeah
they are they're about a little but sunny
well uh i will say that junk i got uh
uh no i got a buddy
yeah there's one the night
and know
yeah
yeah he is alive and
yeah i didn't hear you on that
you know the way it is that
yeah any more money
like it it's sad that there's much of a day
you know your job
know yeah we're gonna do
and and another girl
pardon
no no no um
uh-huh
yeah that one's on running on it
you know
i have no longer and like you know on
really like any time
right
and then you know i had i guess not
hey what's worse
uh i'm uh uh