but to go before do the book
so i'm just going to be day do we need to look into the movie construction joe how are you from
my grandma when really sweet charity
will do we do i they mean you know
they don't they do play on play by that way but i don't know
right no no no no i'm not there and you know a man and a man
and they made them being very demanding around and i mean the man
they don't read all the time they're little combo l._a. man nine
bring a lot of it and then bring a job right now uh and they still operating a man
yeah
i don't think they may or june really be able to
no
set up a job right now oh no no right now i'm doing right now uh
do they pay me right now a lot of
a lot do anything
no