what happened to your hair clara to cut it clean game
calling did did he cut i must too yeah was it crazy is your hair crazy now yeah yeah so the cameras
crazy here yeah like how crazy that is
he save i'm incorrect new clip yeah you didn't raise 'til the cut it for you yeah yeah they higher correct yeah is she gonna cut it short for you
um well here i can't share yep so you know cut your hair in the kitchen is it gonna be cute yeah
it cut chalet shows okay you're going to cut it with my scissors paper
yes only paper temper only pink paper yeah that's the only thing that scissors need to cut huh
nick yeah i mean
these guys make huh yeah i mean and making lakes so
i i really and i like him a letter
no yeah uh sick oh when are we cutting
your hair i got ah rachel gonna cut it tonight guy oh
they really
this guy i work
yeah yeah and they're yeah they are bigger mainly energy
and sharp huh yeah