mm
yes
and i've never he has made him look here's window
hello my name's dawn
why is it that way
um mm mm them to live
little town
no
um england to have any
relax
and i wasn't here not
yeah but um
no no weren't
hi randy mold you don't look my
well how about that show me
right
wow shall we may not even a mile
mount for me
mm mm mm
put me in my head
eleven don't give it a little thing they miss that many
mm mm mm
these are real ring ranging degree
does he work in my and the the and
i don't have my
mm
no i didn't learn anything and they and you don't have time to a window
and uh i mean
mm mhm yeah um and we need to know uh and uh
mm mm go to the bathroom
yeah mm uh uh uh gardening can come yards know uh my uh
mm mm