oh right gets evening evening a lot of the news here are done by tom and also the whole philosophy of the night is the joke painting collection started in nineteen eighty one by california artist and they're still underway projects dealing with yoga consciousness music
mm
yeah and and and and
no i i mean
and and every now and and
no matter
mhm
down to the bell or women and the and don't know when my mom and dad are out on the and those and or or and they're going to die brown down to the and watch you know momma you're them being and the van and rolls when my mom and daddy that is the
and they did back then and then they don't have to stay in the uh the do every day and they day
and then and then and then then and then
and then
mhm mhm mm mm
and and then