you make it on your students yeah borders a promotional real from uh
yeah can't break from the professors were hunting in high school so it's um uh-huh yeah
then you weren't like making or
what before you before they got the collar three not right
good and other coleman we've that could be on and putting out a cliff cliff lotus loaning it'd be the fourth
wow
mhm so noisy yeah yeah wow you don't even i'm and um and those and grandfathers on we don't really know job
mhm yeah she's in i what do you work you yeah you're no
oh mhm
oh my god
mhm
not living not on ago was close to the bomb
the grease make you um
mm mm
no
no not real quick you know it was
wow
too
yeah yeah well that's good though yeah