mm mm
no so your sister last night
from the time that you know
ooh what she's
and you your so by no means but try to you sure your mom and dad
i
you know from
no the or your sister store or you know
uh it's a a point they call a big guy totally praying
not thought about all you
do you know
oh you're a time when he died
i know that here they don't do that now you have a chance to go to middle let your knees
what the
oh like strong to saint
they what happened in the down here for just the the habit hey i'm dr in my lifetime
the
well i've travelled in return them better way by giving them a whole lot of money you can change will let you hope he's got plenty of money doing really good and your target takes money to build and
that
in china china getting back to by law well well the guy but i know he's not in the the last name right go
do you
they do and they they do
oh god yes that'd be me not me might not be fine pretty straightforward explain i can i explain it okay um the that i just found it on the on your underwear and bra door it's pretty much just reasons i think that the catholic church is misery for me
okay ah let me back up indulgences somebody anything
oh i do not that's a bible and that's another problem with the catholic church not wanting the trials
yeah i was kinda whacking on the well they're typical so i'm fine perfectly sober okay bye
come forward at least right
you know write my next martin luther king say that i have to destroy the papers and what what you mean you carry out such ridiculous endeavor indulging in the scriptures that you want your drugs onto that martin luther is correct movement i know
i mean well it can tell explain i can't i mean i
oh
actually my third time
now do you know your time you know
the giants
do you really have an elephant yes it's a white elephant oh what's his name oh no i i see
oh my uh a strong well not get paid three uh john
don't tell me a day try to cut down a long time
oh i
bloodline uh just forget about it you know not
you know you may point peter and i feel the and
yeah
okay sounds good
oh my
the boy or to
wrong
a a
the uh
john
no
or whatever
can we leave send you a paper or broiled salmon
okay fine
see what people are you are they draw you retired
oh can you know it's not the for me to go to my car
um no no non non we're
for a little die they know what's going on and on my mind is about 1 in county
oh i can do they know me too
mhm
you actually see what is it now my mom
made it back from a trial what he was intercepted club on horseback
yeah
nobody seems to know where this very moment
so my mom got her some trust i know i mean to enjoy it later but ah i'm going to ride my third grade work well i see i'm kinda got lost in for a second there take a break this isn't good for you this capital translating see what i mean you need to work on your music music you know beautiful music the profits second sauce and oklahoma's beautiful magnificent things that god's given us you know you don't get me my right here yeah thanks let's see that's how long ago
mm mm mm
mhm
oh right
no
oh oh more
to go to work
and armed with crew
on earth is not is he own strengths con by are driving would be who who who say we're not the the man of god who's saying staff screws that may be crises lasted is he his name from age to really and he when i
and those to
well not be here for his to try
uh uh
prince of darkness
for him his age we can
for for his or
a bad word uh no thanks to them no to him with us ah go i also know bodies they may to god truth all by hearing some news for a