not them do a little frightening how like someone that really
anyway
oh
yeah
yeah and i'm like oh you're damned them older ireland down
but i yeah
i mean like
yeah and that's very yeah uh-huh
have to hold her face and tell him to hold their reading about er totally self
right
you could just seen the dots or whatever
driving and they're going to
oh it is a good idea yeah oh yeah
and how to have monitor wonder why
right
yeah
hello
yeah yeah really
oh i mean
oh you mean
i'm driving
even now
okay
and i love that people like your your height the money and then okay gotcha
maybe one day she knows where they
green or anything
horse
and you're going to
oh okay
yeah i haven't kept once in yeah
across the bridge