do you mean they they the whole legal and then they
i'm a i'm a say in the day and then the other one
a- and then there was a day and then try to stay on
um and that that that
no
i i don't know i'm
in new
and i'm in utah
mm
wow
uh
and
to me kind of looking and they asked around and say no no no no i'm not a fan so no about that
okay and then i don't know a little too much and here
go to those and then we are going to tell you gossiping
mhm
mean you don't get it today and polluted and many times i was a little young i think it's a nice i didn't know that i do and
no i mean he was telling me that i didn't do it somebody saw them they do that any time you saw that he got a
we did have to do that have be on you know i don't know
how did you have anybody to get to know and then something you know
which one
really
my you don't about you know what i know i'm not a my pin numbers of people a
and um
i i didn't know it gets done know
my name's michael
that may or may not much a kind of
know
i mean i know then you'll come up here and that was one thing i
that kind of money
they don't really keep in mind
and the number i mean i'm not
and uh
mhm
and then we will see you know enough time to do that they they can give you a for news and and
that i i wouldn't mind could you know
my name is michael from other things like that and they know whatever
so how'd you need to make money
um
ooh
i
yeah
mhm
you know
yeah
and uh
no
and you know owning your canoeing that can take i people will be due to done countries have on but it's that i don't know meal uh how do you need to find all kinds and switzerland promoted to go see it as that
you know
and you know people she enjoys that live in i did that baby doing nothing for me to
dad
uh
you got you know to the
no
you know it doesn't
i could always that could you know to to watch it on and he was
for me and and and
um and and be
in the navy
me too
um
nice to me
and and
and do it
and he has no
and uh and
hi canoeing i seen
from all around the house sold household
come to some entertainment and whatnot
mhm
how do you like to see if i wanted i wanted to give you something that i had i need to go to school i didn't either
mm mm
a long way
or or or or or
tax on anyway um so we can listen to me i'm i'm not old enough and a day
and whatever and um and they and um
really
okay
they
we're really
that
wow so
we do that
kind of hanging around
a little bit on the border and every now and and our daughter and a no i'm in the and
everything