no
okay
the organization that name by the the to the to the back they do the carry on the reading reading a for eight nine ten eleven twelve point
the the biggest the my son small amount of time it is very very heavy workout probably six or so and then you have the ladies that are going on the money that's coming on or anything
the last twenty or thirty years and my family my dad's number my brother's coming back
little girl i learned how to make my grandma my longest lenders you're not that i'm thirty nine yeah
i don't know your opinion i i said no no no no no they need to go for the money they make a man
this is one big one weekend
we have going on