every movie would be a i really enjoyed the stories in the stores and told the symbolism and just the concept was how it's done the characters it was just real great movie
uh i really like um l._a. confidential um say spring love and catch up again
i think that my favorite movie would probably be
angels or hanging over my least favorite movie honestly i really don't make enough to watch that movie and i really i can't really say i've seen that movie i wouldn't be able to answer
i hate every movie that has um kevin costner in it
close ties between the blair witch project and
my favorite genre i really like action and the war
um comedy
movies is probably comedy or action i revere robert deniro voice many different characters he can pull up
such excellent and especially like in when once upon a time
i really like um we're dicaprio work
i don't pay attention to the actor's name so i wouldn't really
i really wanted to see a movie when i'll be able to go into another world no matter what it is and the best thing about it is another person made another person was capable
bring someone else into another world the story telling us just brilliant and
the thing that makes me want to see a movie is probably the trailers or just
that if i read something about
if my friends really wanna see it or if i like the trailer or the movie i go see it
thing i imagine for the future movies is that
i think that they're gonna get like bad movies and occasionally there would be
for the future movies there's going to be a lot more original ideas and a lot more people taking original ideas but within they know that tradition of there's definitely going to be a level excellent
no matter how it's done they're definitely going to be
um
me