she on her head way
that is
so
bridge to the florida keys bridge
amateur worded baby's smart enjoyed her job because she loves babies babies
that is
imagine
laura their parents will allow them to go to the
imagine that
you were to suggest the students at my school we suggest that the school system purchase more computers suggest
so
your word is treasure the museums greatest trailer into recently honors ancient rome statue treasure
you are to treasure
at this point well was asked to leave the room when i went to lots more words including population and apology and some other ones i couldn't hear she got lots of compliments on her spelling and especially on her place congratulations