richard carpet outlet to look at carpeting 'cause we're looking to redo our living room we're on old furniture that we've had since we got married and had had since she was a kid
couch discovered in cover is twenty five years old going through three covers from us and ready for a new one with the rug and see we can get a good idea
mm mm
when you like and it's half price right close to yeah
cool
okay
you can't see piling smile agreement but it's it's not like the cyber stepping on the so anyway i like it a lot we can have a or a neutral couch and then we can do all these pieces to screw yeah can you see the difference in like this year this bluish pizzas um i definitely more and they're kind of give it to be
oh yeah sure i'm talking about right there i can see that and it all the time
mhm
did you get an option for you know had had back
you probably like a in the back of your head would fit perfectly
really cool to watch shows
not only watch it is true see the complimentary green that i'm sitting at work it's short too got plenty of room for popcorn so yeah that's too much room
no
so this is actually fine right now harmless chair to couch pillows and then there's a lot of men that also push push up next to in between next to the longer seats new couch
so it's really nice not fake