some speaker phone and i live in you love me this i can i can find
um and women are beautiful
is last june and candles out of bed and not a good topic today about i'll be back to them but i
i can i can you know i just buy one and carries the confidence i'm not sure if i'll be helping a ton of money the but
the bad old age don't they haven't found the god no bills a little
no no not yet i'm fine you can talk too much my all the time i don't think they do all that means a lot more now you know they go in and we were young mom and my mom said oh
and i live in the same time
they've come a time when my mom and dad i don't know how that goes along yeah yeah that was a man i'm retired i don't buy that are on your mind you know i'm not know man with a lot of 'em and say ten dollars i'm like oh no no no no no no no no just the dog
i can live on line
um
mhm