and uh
and and and and and
no no no no no no no no no no they don't want to
okay were you in our neighbors they were they just want the the wheels so and the fact that people don't think the thing about read all about reality making noise during the day without me knowing that we do watch them because they didn't even know why do maybe some people to buy her way to get the give them do feel the same thing that was going to name same game and dr in order to read now everybody getting i'm getting ten dollars an hour
provider dialing parties tiny type wait till now they're they don't want to
everything on the name people keep know more than just going to get you an
you know like nobody really knows never right now we know where i live in maybe we're not like when i was on line and they're going to make dinner on the other thing out there and they were they were out there in the you know
try to provide for my retirement trying to represent noticed they don't want to
every day on the name numbers on that get you on the
like nobody really knows how right right they live and i was thinking maybe we're not like on line it's like on on the news i try to learn how to enter and they were in our power