is it a demonstration on how to go to eat in through the underwater housing up is pretty good t._v. instead of through in you're ready to put it in uh
can be helpful please make sure the length area
um okay what's that going through that he gets it's glided business so
so we like we like
make sure you have to clip them locked into place
um
immaturity kept presses and so we lived into place and locket securely
now you're devious ready for dining use to ten on t._v. here's the on but then
yeah that's back what you mean with the t._v. so tempted covered in operated in me with this button and
include it um just like on this menu fucking
do you to travel it's recommended to install protected piece back on so that when i get presents when you're traveling
mhm