and uh
and when they announced tony llama around
ah no way i try to i guess
uh i guess
no my mom my mom was a man and da da da da da da da
really
um but no one to buy 'em as much ground gang can change every day
job by that i can
you know like when you're going i'm going to do that
yeah
on i'm not a bad but i i think you're right i'm trying to live in a bar or go but i other and
your mom why is that i'm like god
no no no no but i'm on sorry
ah no i'm uh
and and and i'm around and around
no no no no i remember trying the next day
uh i guess i do
mom and mom so worried about 'em so long as to to go on the line
um
they
um no i live by a round gangs and training every day
i'm fine
you are on for a while you know whatever i'm going to going to that
no
um i i think it's very and and know what i'm going to live in a bar or go through with it either
well you know why i'm going to put the
well i know i'm gonna i'm on
um i'm a guy a uh
ah on or a
mm mm