used furniture for education research into reality out there
and we thoroughly on the market now to highlights we live on the screen it or climate changes down in and
because you will be easily loaded onto your downright once then you can either use uh graffiti location by looking through your chart
so
you would see the teaching the fellow
what state are you afraid of and and even
the which color and it's easy to just
no
you can change their
and already made it
you also have to go straight to the they can directory they by adding it you can view it just said they would show you the areas that you can pay
you get a pop up where it is what it looks like like if you like twenty so and even if you want me you could actually see the cussing but you which is the way the phone create the digital t._v. company called
uh well we went through the project and they would realize most run into reality there was no way that we could see where are you okay and then we kind of program called which great reality that we can we create some graffiti dirtiest mix and then use your credit using accustomed to create a or an by having a few different
the same thing
also we the old fun not just touch screen fulltime credit application from nine own yourself making this little all the same function pages to sleep and drop option of we wanted to to find the campaign
and um i