hi i'm joy
yeah
oh
hi pam i'm in that you should come to
point again she still shells on she me that'll match i you know
i can't see me kids uh she found me five definitely not to be checked outside
you get on your body she i'd already mommy and daddy said
so i don't know you don't even talk yeah
she she'd
oh gosh me fly she met on each had income now she eats it said
illness so simple and she says i guess chicken popping so foolish amusement dopey chess teaching i'll see it down
yeah
yeah no pay thirty or
yeah okay right
yeah right yeah i guess
oh yeah oh gee i say no
please take care no jeeze
yeah they love me as well
well not real sad that sad that all day and age that oh no oh god oh he
but um that i've done that
i think miserable shooting somebody from ah it's on me and i'm not told us we didn't know unfortunate by that
ouch ouch
i didn't see that and eat well i should try that maybe um
yeah um well let's try that
he's not enough of that one machine
mhm
backing she's been you know
by
oh that he's uh
no
absolutely i know well yeah
nice died though my uh
yeah no i didn't eat close too
no um no not
okay
how did he most out of course a dog okay
oh gee
oh yeah they're middle hey hey
that goes back and change landlord you
be my gosh so did hey hey
no i mean who she is uh
i thought that we all do you want to be
no i haven't found them
yeah
no well it isn't that funny
yeah that'd be one
um
no i mean they have
that
dawn
oh really
oh no
oh yeah
he's taken online