can get boy get blown out again and
mhm yep and all that
i doubt that hit the supply that based
i've had that uh uh uh
did you watch
ah right ah
oh okay
yeah no doubt no doubt kate stole the taliban that lately that ball ball ball that she'll know booming
they get get along
and that that point um
so i ended up space
and i said besides the mole
so gosh um
right i'm
so of me uh came to the future but trauma and audit best strong enough to lady extra loan
we got a bad and we got the and i don't know i mean you've got the beep god aid wiped out blooming tiring
and then
yeah he died
yum yup yup yup can we go camping
yeah we don't think so i don't know of course you know
and if she didn't know
baseball fan but i'm saying
hi kim
think you can't you can't board cutting you gotta get them