no all that
no no
hi
right
okay
back
you know there was the same time off work
no you're fine fine
bake a
go away
that's true
i'm going to trial i always felt i felt bad because
boy
and they're just that space fucking make 'em pay just a job i'm trying to tell them
but on the plane
swimming on right now
so
i wish i your what's your go back and don't break your guy
oh
no i don't know i don't know why
they've been taught wrong about that
so many fucking
yeah i don't know i just
no but sexy
way back
yeah
right right
right they are going on
is it
yeah
oh we're going to be aware of what's going on
that's right
yeah i don't really know i try not to go to class no you are going to do on tape
hot springs jamie
we had our
okay
yeah
you gotta totally troy gosh burglar bars so i don't know
it was two broken
okay
uh right now our our son
right right
to watch like
keep her she got arm
they're pretty crazy
getting to be tough them
around my wife
you know
yeah
just because the
really close
i didn't i didn't i didn't the uh the the second one yeah first
no i don't know if i can see
yeah
oh my god the the last one i saw a bill
and they enjoy
yeah it did what say somebody
which is called trying to get i mean
drop dead gorgeous but your jacket
okay
yeah
wanna go
dollar
buffet taller redemption that much
oh the one hand sometimes they come in and i'm not very type